Andrew Venson

vensoneandrew@gmail.com 512-450-4101 Round Rock, Texas

Summary

Experienced in writing well designed, testable, efficient code by using best software development practices. Skilled in creating website layout/user interfaces by using standard HTML/CSS practices. Also skilled in developing intuitive creative web interactions with multiple JavaScript libraries. Competent in integrating data from various back-end services and databases.

Education

University of Texas at Austin

Full Stack Web Development • Austin, Texas

11/2020

Austin Community College

Computer Programming • Austin, Texas

Skills

- ReactJS
- JQuery
- PHP
- T-SQL
- CSS
- Selenium
- GitHub

- JavaScript
- Python
- · MySQL
- HTML5
- Bootstrap
- Test Automation
- Git

Experience

Smartwebs

Software Tester • Round Rock, Texas

10/2019 - 12/2019

Built automated test framework with JavaScript and Sahi automation tools to test Mobile application across Android platform using Android Studios.

IT In a Pinch

Developer Lead • Austin, Texas

04/2019 - 05/2019

Built web reporting utility using Flask, Python, and MySQL for the backend. Used JavaScript/jQuery, HTML, and CSS for developing the frontend. Deployed Application to CentOS 7 server using Nginx and WSGI services.

CRS Solutions

Computer Software Technician • Austin, Texas

04/2019 - 09/2019

Lead all Focus Point of Sale projects. Installed, configured and programmed innovative menus. Developed internal scripts using Python. Trained staff and provided remote support.

Austin POS

Computer software technician • Austin, Texas

10/2016 - 04/2019

Installed, configured and programmed innovative Point of Sale menus. Developed internal scripts. Trained staff, and provided remote support.